▍2026 辛辛那提 WTA1000 1/8决赛
佩古拉 6-2 4-6 7-5 科斯蒂亚 · 赛后场上采访
this time.
这一次，
Pegula books a place in the last eight
佩古拉锁定1/4决赛席位，
in Cincy for the third time in five seasons.
五个赛季里第三次打到这里。
What a struggle.
过程太不容易了。
There'll be a warm exchange at the net.
网前两人温暖地拥抱。
Might be Cirstea's last ever appearance
这可能是科斯蒂亚
in Cincinnati, but it's going to be one
在辛辛那提的最后一次亮相，
that we will remember for quite a while.
但会让人记很久。
Pegula eventually gets over the line having
佩古拉最终跨过了终点线，
missed multiple opportunities.
尽管此前错过了好几次机会。
The fight of Cirstea, but Pegula prevails.
拼到最后，赢的是佩古拉。
The number three seed is through 75
三号种子七比五拿下决胜盘，
in the third to the court.
闯进下一轮。
Jesse, you are just so tough,
杰西，你实在是太顽强了，
so hard to to beat.
太难被打败了。
She threw everything she had at you
她把所有招都用来对付你，
in essentially nothing to lose season,
反正也没什么可失去的，
but here you are standing here.
但站到最后的还是你。
What did you do?
你是怎么做到的？
Yeah, I mean
是啊，我是说，
that was really tough being up a set
领先一盘之后真的很难熬，
and I think a break or I don't know what it
好像还破发一次，记不清了，
was, but I was winning the whole time
但那段时间我一直在赢，
and I had a feeling
我隐约觉得，
that she was going to loosen up
她会慢慢放开手脚，
and start hitting some and raise her level
打出更好的球，提升水平，
and hit some better shots and she did.
她确实做到了。
I felt like I just lost the momentum
我感觉自己在第二盘末尾
at the end of that second, but credit to her.
丢了节奏，但这要归功于她。
She started playing, you know,
她开始打得，你知道的，
I think much better, serving much better.
好很多，发球也好很多。
So,
所以，
and then it just felt like tricky conditions
第三盘感觉条件变得很棘手，
in the third.
很难适应。
Honestly, it was weird.
说实话，感觉有点怪。
We were breaking a lot.
我们互相破发了好多次。
It was really windy.
风真的很大。
I felt like we were returning well.
我感觉两人的接发都不错，
It was just really hard to kind
所以真的很难
of defend off the serve.
靠发球去防守。
Even when you hit a good serve,
哪怕发出了一记好球，
I felt like with the wind,
在风里我也感觉
I was just a little tentative on some volleys
有些截击球上有点犹豫，
and overheads and swing volleys,
高压和摆浪截击也是，
and that can get really tough
那样真的很难受，
and you start secondguessing yourself.
会开始怀疑自己。
But, I think I did a good job there
不过我觉得自己在最后
at the end to kind of just push myself
做得不错，逼着自己
a little bit to to be as aggressive as possible.
尽可能地打得更主动一点。
And it worked.
而且真的奏效了。
I don't think you mind me asking you
我猜你不会介意
something about Sorana.
我问几句关于索拉娜的事。
She's been on tour for 22 years.
她在巡回赛打了二十二年。
The first time you played,
你们第一次交手，
we're talking 17-year-old Jesse in Midland.
还是在米德兰，十七岁的你。
But to see her consistency from one
但看着她这么多年
of the most consistent players on tour,
是巡回赛最稳定的选手之一，
I'm sure you respect what she's doing right
我相信你尊重她
now.
现在在做的事。
Oh, yeah, for sure.
哦，那当然。
I mean, she's someone that I have known
我是说，我认识她
since we were playing challengers
还是打挑战赛的时候，
and I've seen her come up
我看着她一路
through the rankings
打上排名榜，
and then get hurt and come back
然后受伤又复出，
and then obviously now kind
现在很明显
of on a little bit of a farewell tour.
算是打一场小小的告别巡演。
We'll see depending
接下来怎么样
on how well she's doing.
要看她自己打得怎么样了。
She's doing pretty well.
她现在打得还挺好的。
But I know she said that, you know,
但我知道她说过，
this wants to be her last year,
她希望这是她最后一年，
but I've always had the utmost respect
但我一直对她
for her.
抱着最高的敬意。
She's always super professional,
她一直特别职业，
super nice, just courteous,
特别好相处，也很有礼貌，
and I feel like is is kind of the epitome
我觉得她差不多就是
of like a a professional tennis player
一个职业网球运动员
should be, and I've always
该有的样子，我也一直
had that to to be around, you know,
很庆幸身边有这样的人，
since we've been playing with each other.
因为我们打过很多次交手。
So, I haven't played her in a really long time
不过很久没跟她交手了，
as well.
也是真的。
So, beautifully said.
这话说得真好。
Yeah, it's been about five years
是啊，距离你们上一次交手
since the two of you have played.
差不多已经五年了。
Got to ask just a couple
还得问你几个
of personal questions just getting all up
有点私人的问题，
in your business.
打探一下你的生活。
So, after every match,
每次比赛结束以后，
you have a fascinating routine.
你都有一套很有意思的流程。
Is it
是不是
the same every time you open something,
每次都一样，先打开东西，
you put something on your hand,
在手上戴点什么，
you check your phone?
然后看看手机？
Do you
你有没有
have a consistent postmatch routine there
一套固定的赛后流程，
at the bench?
就在场边？
Yes, I put my wedding ring back
有的，我会先把婚戒
on and I power up my phone
戴回去，再打开手机，
and then I usually come and talk to you.
然后一般就会过来跟你聊天。
That's pretty much it.
基本就这些。
And honestly,
说实话，
this is putting my ring on is out of habit
戴戒指纯粹是习惯，
because I lose a lot of things.
因为我特别爱丢东西。
And I have actually lost this before.
这枚戒指我之前真的丢过。
And by an absolute miracle,
说来是个奇迹，
story for another day,
这个故事改天再讲，
I found it like in the street.
我居然在街上把它找回来了。
somebody found it.
是有人捡到还给了我。
And so my husband was not very happy
所以我丈夫当时
with that, as you can imagine.
很不高兴，你能想象的。
So I've become very habitual
所以我现在已经很习惯，
with putting my wedding ring back
会把婚戒戴回去，
on because he knows, everyone
因为他知道，认识我的人
that knows me knows I just lose stuff all
都知道我总是丢三落四，
the time,
一直如此，
except tennis matches.
除了网球比赛不会输。
One more quick thing.
再问最后一个小问题。
It's interesting.
有点意思。
I I've known you for a long time,
我认识你这么久了，
but I have no clue what the answer
但完全猜不到
to this question will be.
这个问题的答案。
What's playing in your headphones
你走上球场的时候，
when you walk out on court?
耳机里放的是什么？
Do you have a walk out song
有没有固定的出场曲，
or does it change all the time?
还是一直在换？
It changes.
一直在换。
I feel like with usually like a week
一般大概一两周
or two it might stay the same.
会维持不变。
I don't know.
我也说不好。
Right now
现在这段时间
it's it's always pretty relaxing music
放的一直是比较放松的音乐，
that like more viby, not super intense,
氛围感更强，不会太激烈，
not super rap.
也不是那种劲爆说唱。
I listen to like a lot of R&B.
我听挺多R&B的，
Sometimes it's afrobeat.
有时候是非洲节拍。
Sometimes it's Yeah.
有时候是……对。
Something really laidback.
反正就是很放松的那种。
So, this week I don't even know what it
这周放的是什么
I don't even know.
我自己都说不上来。
I think it's Amber Mark.
好像是安柏·马克。
I don't know if that's her name.
也不确定是不是她的名字。
I think that's her name.
应该是这个名字。
I don't know. She's not very well known yet.
不确定，她现在还没名气。
I'm waiting for her to blow up.
我就等着她红起来。
I should probably know her name
我大概应该记住她的名字，
though if I'm waiting for that to happen.
毕竟我都在等这一天了。
But she's been really good
但她真的写得很好，
and I've been listening to a lot of her.
我最近听了她很多歌。
Well, she will blow up
那她肯定会红的，
since you just gave her a shout out.
毕竟你刚给她打了广告。
As much variety in her music
她音乐里的多样性，
as in her game.
和她球风里的一样丰富。
Show some love for Jessica Pegula.
把掌声送给佩古拉。